离他远点  远点
Stay away! Stay away!
这人是怎么逃出来的
How did this man get away?
在处理时
During processing.
出了差错
A mistake.
他还没被感染
He's not contaminated.
无风险
No risks.
准备火化
Prepare it for incineration!
带我回实验室
Get me back to the facility.
该死
Oh, shit.
莫斯科  黑熊监狱
这是个误会
我是联安局的
我知道
伊林呢
都烂的发臭了
尸体在你后备箱里
他本来就臭气熏天
见钱眼开的走狗
需要我出马吗
You want me to have a shot?
你们连威胁人的本事都没有
'Cause your people skills suck.
我朋友逃走了是吧
So my friend got away, huh?
他很快就会赶回来
Pretty soon he's gonna come back
把我们救出去的
and then we're gonna get out of here.
你是说钻进我们卡车里的那位朋友吗
The same friend we found in one of our trucks?
达米恩·斯科特中士  我看你是活腻了
Sergeant Damien Scott, you have a death wish?
先是杀了我老板的儿子
First you kill my boss' son,
还跟皮拉戈娃上校的女儿暗通款曲
then you team up with Colonel Pirogov's daughter.
带走
这就是你所谓的"出马"?
"Want me to give it a shot", huh?
别这么做  我跟她合不来的
You don't want to do that. We really don't get along.
美国佬在开玩笑呢
你说什么
What'd you say?
说你只有一个睾丸
That you only have one testicle.
都怪你[是留着给你的]
It's all for you.
上校  你跟我们保证
Colonel, you assured us
莫斯科  20号分部
你的手下会阻止安德森攻入网络中枢
your men could prevent Andersson breaching the hub.
我的手下还在执行任务
My men are still in the field.
这项任务...
This mission is--
已经失败了
They failed!
情报显示  朱海瑞的人
We have intel that prisoners are being moved
不断地将黑熊监狱中的囚犯转移走
from Black Bear on behalf of Al-Zuhari.
转去哪里  为了什么
Where to? And what for?
我们还不清楚
Well, we don't know yet.
我们没有空中支援  长官
We have no sat cover, ma'am.
我需要北约在波兰东部边境的无人机
NATO has drones on Poland's eastern border and I need them.
越过俄罗斯领空吗
Over Russian air space?
恕我直言
Well, with respect,
我对交朋友不感兴趣
I'm not in the business of making friends.
我只是在阻止一场即将发生的恐怖袭击
I'm just trying to prevent an attack that we know is coming!
你得先掌握更详细的情报...
Until you have more detailed information--
没有无人机办不到  长官
Well, without drones, I can't get it, sir!
上校  你的手下现在在哪
Where are your men now, Colonel?
上次联络时
Well, the last we heard,
他们正在从黑熊监狱撤退
they were on their way out of Black Bear.
一旦有了更详细的情报  我会通知你们
As soon as I have more detailed intel, you'll be fully briefed.
上校  你可以调遣那些无人机
You'll get your drones, Colonel.
遵命  长官们
Sir, ma'am.
你跟这几个混蛋有过节啊
So you got history with these assholes?
过节?
History?
阿卡帝·乌尔诺夫杀了我父亲
Arkady Ulyanov murdered my father.
我操
Fuck me.
-愈发有趣了  -这我可以保证
- This is gonna end well. - I guarantee it.
封闭房间
Seal the room.
求你们  不
Please. No.
不要
No!
注入病原
Use Vector Strain.
他正在发烧
He's running a fever.
可能患有呼吸道疾病
Looks like there are respiratory problems.
那就处理掉吧
Ah, dispose of him.
没汽油了
在这停车
把手机放下
知道了
你说他是去给我们买薯片了吗
You think he's gonna buy us a bag of chips?
少自作聪明
Don't be smart-ass.
你能帮我转告吗  我喜欢烤肉味的
You gonna ask him for me? I like the barbecue ones.
你想吃子弹吗
You want bullet?
接着说啊
Keep talking.
那乌尔诺夫怎么办
How's that gonna go down with Ulyanov?
他想要活的  不是吗
Wants me for himself, doesn't he?
弄断他手指
那傻逼斯基说什么
What did Fuckoffski say?
想弄断这根吗
Oh, you gonna break that?
操  搞毛啊
Fuck! What is this?
-拿手机  -拿着呢
- Bring the phone! - I'm trying!
你说什么  能说英语吗
What are you saying? Say it in English.
-操他妈的混蛋  -说的没错
- Fucking asshole. - Yeah, he is.
快走  快走  等等
Get out, get out. Oh, wait!
-快走  -来了
- Come on. - I'm coming!
来了
Coming.
我要跑到那辆车后面  没问题吧
I'm gonna go after that car, all right?
-好  -准备
- Yeah. - Ready to run?
-行动  -好
- Coming? - Yeah.
蹲下
Down.
行动  走
Coming? Go!
蹲下蹲下  快上车
Down, down, down, down. OK. Get in the car.
上车
Get in.
坐过去  我来开
Move over 'cause I'm driving.
那你倒是上车啊
Well, get in the car, then.
上车
Get in!
操你妈
Motherfucker!
开枪  开枪
Shoot! Shoot!
-漂亮  -闭嘴好好开车
- Nice! - Just shut up and drive.
人抓到了吗
一个在德列兹纳
另一个逃了
蠢货
我搞砸了
I've fucked up.
完蛋了
I fucked up.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
我必须向乌尔诺夫供出你的人
I had to give Ulyanov your men.
是我泄露他们在黑熊监狱的
I've told him they were at Black Bear.
什么
What?
菲利普  他不相信我
Philip, he didn't trust me.
我当时进退两难
I was in a corner.
不得不给他们点真实情报
I had to give him something real.
你利用了迈克尔和达米恩
You used Michael and Damien.
我只是利用了手头的资源
I used what I had,
跟你利用我一样
as you use me.
那你都问出了哪些东西
Right. Well, tell me what you know.
他们把犯人运到哪里去
Where are they taking the prisoners?
他在黑熊监狱北面有个实验室
He has a facility north of Black Bear.
具体地点  北边多远
Give me the location. How far north?
我不知道
I don't know.
是什么实验室
Well, what kind of facility?
-生化实验室  -具体是...
- It's bio-chemical. - Yeah, and what do they--
我就只知道这些
That's all I know!
菲利普
Philip,
我不能刨根问底
I couldn't press him any harder.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
你不好意思?
You're sorry?
立即回总部
You get back here now.
你打算怎么弄开
What are you gonna do with that?
操
Oh, fuck.
该死
Shit!
你总是在关键的时候掉链子
You always run out at the worst possible time.
别开玩笑
No kidding.
看来你是逃不出我的手掌心了
Well, it looks like you're stuck with me.
棒极了
Great.
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
给20号分部打个电话
Get 20 on that phone.
乌尔诺夫为什么要杀你老爸
Why did Ulyanov kill your dad?
因为他是一个正直的人
Because he was an honest man.
给
There.
谢了
Thank you.
我是马丁内斯
Martinez.
是斯科特
I have Scott!
开扬声器
On speaker.
说吧  中士  有什么新情况
Go ahead, Sergeant. What have you got for me?
我跟皮戈拉娃在一起  哦  是皮拉戈娃
I'm with Pigarover. Heh! Pirogova.
我们现在黑熊监狱东面的某处
We're somewhere east of Black Bear.
斯顿布奇呢  断了联系
Stonebridge? I lost him.
他们把安德森押上了转运卡车
They put Andersson on one of those prison transport trucks.
阿迈跟去了  我没拉住他
Mikey went after him. I couldn't stop him.
我们现在多了空中支援
Well, we have eyes in the sky.
你知道大概位置吗
Any idea where we should be looking?
不知道
Negative.
迈克的身体状况很差
Mike's in a pretty bad way.
可能是胸腔里出了毛病
I think it's in his chest.
如今他呼吸都有困难了
He's having difficulty breathing.
那得抓紧时间找到他
Then we haven't got long to find him.
斯科特  尽快归队
Get back as soon as, Scott.
该死
Shit!
收到  我得挂了  得甩掉几个警察
Yeah, copy that. I got to go. I got to lose some cops.
拿着
Take that.
已锁定斯科特的手机信号
Have a lock on Scott's signal.
行动
Go.
过来
Come here.
坐下
Sit down! Sit!
这是什么地方  我们在哪
What is this place? Where the fuck are we?
是研究所  在德列兹纳
It's a research facility. In Drezna.
研究什么
What kind of research?
我只是助手  我不知道
I'm only an assistant. I don't know!
放你妈的屁
Bullshit!
从事生物研究
It's biological.
研究天花病毒的生化武器
Weaponized smallpox.
糟糕
Shit.
把电话给我
Give me your phone.
我们不准带电话
They're not permitted.
只有竹中博士有手机
Only Dr. Takenaka has a phone.
带我...
Take me.
带我去见安德森
Take me to Andersson.
就是那个跟我一起来的人  带我去见他
He's the man I came in with. Take me to him.
你快不行了
You're dying.
我可以帮忙
I could help.
我可以帮你
I could help you.
带我去见安德森
Just take me to Andersson.
就现在
Now.
-他们追上来了 -别废话
- They're gaining. - No shit.
除非你停止嘲笑我的蛋蛋...
Anytime you want to stop busting my balls--
或是你口中仅剩的蛋...
or ball, as you put it-- you can.
老娘说烦了会告诉你的
I'll let you know when I'm finished.
你不觉得压力山大吗
Do you feel threatened?
宝贝儿  大爷我吃的牛排都比你的老
I've eaten tougher steaks than you, sweetheart.
昨天那个女人
That woman yesterday.
那个人质吗
The hostage?
朱莉娅  你就不觉得困扰吗
Julia, it didn't bother you?
金  这里不是缉毒局
Kim, this is not the DEA.
不是什么都有法可依
It's not about the law.
事情并非只有黑白之分
Things aren't black and white.
我知道世界是灰色的
I understand gray. I do.
我也当过卧底
What? I've served undercover.
也干过颇受争议的事
Did some questionable things.
我可以忍受杀掉警卫
Now, I can live with killing that guard
并接听他女友的电话
and hearing his girl on the phone,
但我从来没有亲眼看着
but I have never stood by
无辜妇女被枪毙  却还袖手旁观
and watched an innocent woman executed like that before.
你是要让我认清世界的复杂吗
Is this where you tell me we live in a complicated world?
世界也可以很简单
Or a very simple one.
凡事看开点
It gets easier.
是啊
Yeah.
信号中断
Lost signal.
该往哪走
So? Which way now?
那是黑熊监狱的车
That car is from Black Bear.
-你往哪儿开  -我也不知道
- Where are you going? - I have no idea.
快没油了
We're almost out of fuel.
该死
Shit.
你就不能找辆加满油的车吗
You couldn't have picked a car with a full tank, could you?
没错  抱歉我该先加满油
Yeah, sorry, I should have filled up with gas
检查下油表再偷车的
and checked the oil before I stole it.
哎哟  美国佬学会讽刺了
Ooh, sarcasm from an American.
你以为我们不会?
What, you think we don't get it?
得了吧  地球人都知道[你们不会]
Oh, come on. Everybody knows this.
想搞歧视是吧
You want to do stereotypes?
你也许现在如花似玉  但地球人都知道
You might look good now, sweetheart, but everybody knows
俄罗斯女人老了都会变成又矮又胖
all Russian women turn into short, fat little grannies
戴头巾长胡渣的老太婆
who wear head scarves and have mustaches.
我现在已经能看出点征兆了
I can see one starting now.
巴布什卡[女用头巾, 源自俄语, 本意为老太婆]
Babushka.
-什么  -是我们特有的叫法
- What?  -That's how we call them.
看吧  连名字都有了  那肯定是真的
See? You even got a name for them. Must be true.
你开去那么高的地方干嘛
Why are you going up there?
还有别的路可选吗
You see any other fuckin' road around here?
操
Fuck!
快点出来  快
Come here. Come here. Come on.
等下  过来
Whoa! Come here.
-赶快  你干嘛  -等一下
- Hurry! What? - One second.
-快点  -快
- Come on! - Quick, quick.
好了  他们上当了
All right. They take the bait.
那个爆炸堪称完美
That's an outstanding explosion.
又来警察了
More cops?
那些人不是警察
Those aren't cops.
警察  黑熊警卫  乌尔诺夫
Cops. Black Bear guards. Ulyanov.
还有你没惹上的人吗
Is there anyone you haven't pissed off yet?
如果你还爱我就没有了
Just as long as you still love me.
你上哪去
Where are you going?
那是谁
Who is that?
来的正是时候
Nice timing.
那是我的朋友
That's friends of mine.
-我们得走出去  好吗  -真的假的
- We're gonna walk out there, all right? - Are you?
-相信我  -什么
- Trust me. - What?
相信我就行  你想被困死在这吗
Just trust me. You want to die stuck here, hmm?
-你说呢  -你当然不想
- You tell me. - You don't.
学我做  走
Do what I do. Walk.
看到斯科特
Eyes on Scott.
伙计们
Fellas?
没武器  没枪
Unarmed. No gun.
把枪放下  放下
Put your gun down. Put it down.
就放那  放下
Right there. Down.
跪下  他交给你了
Down on your knees. You got him?
好
Yeah.
干得不错  大妈
Nice work, Babushka.
别高兴的太早
Don't get overexcited.
我看到你收他钱了
人渣
皮拉戈娃少校
Major Pirogova.
他给你惹麻烦了吗
He give you any trouble?
-你说谁  -她爱死我了
- Who? - Ah, she loves me.
-这还用问吗  -很高兴你们及时出现
- Clearly. - Nice of you guys to show up.
你们没事吧
Are you all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
去找迈克吗
Shall we go find Michael?
就这么定了
Let's do it.
你对我做了什么
What have you done to me?
你上哪去了
Where have you been?
-小心  -过来
- Watch out! - Come here.
想我了吗  别
You miss me? Don't!
别跑  不然我割了他喉咙
Don't you run, or I'll slit his throat.
把手机给我
Give me your phone.
交给我左手
Put it in my left hand.
对
Yeah.
他不会杀我的  他要留我活口
He won't do it. He needs me alive.
走  快走
Go! Go!
别走  不准走
Don't do that! Don't do that!
你得救我出去
You have to get me out of here!
不能救
You can't.
他被感染了  会传染
He's infected, contagious.
你一定还有办法救我
There must be something you can do!
他活不了几个小时了
He'll be dead in hours.
是天花  对吗
That's smallpox, right?
是变种
A variant.
毒性更强
Much, much more effective.
更强?
Huh? Effective?
要是这东西到了朱海瑞手上
If al-Zuhari gets his hands on this,
会害死数千人
thousands of people will die.
上万人
Tens of thousands.
为什么
But why?
你又不是信徒[伊斯兰教]
You're not even a believer.
-为了什么  为了钱?  -为了科学
- What is it, money? - Science.
过来  过来
Come here. Come here.
艾瑞克  你认真听我说
Erik, I need you to listen to me.
我需要你告诉我
I need you to tell me
你所知道有关他们计划的一切
everything you know about their plans.
你会让我自生自灭  是吗
You're going to leave me here, aren't you?
你听到他的话了
You heard what he said.
我不能让你出来
I can't let you out,
但我尽可能帮你
but I will get you some help.
任何我能做到的  我都会做  但现在
Anything that I can do, I will do, but right now,
你必须告诉我  你所知道关于他们的一切
you have to tell me everything that you know about them.
你听懂了吗
Do you understand me?
明白  我下载了北约在欧洲所有基地的详细情报
Yeah. I downloaded details of every NATO base in Europe:
时间表  人事档案
schedules, personnel files,
人员清单  地图
manifests, maps.
有迹象表明他们打算袭击哪里吗
Was there any indication on where they plan the attacks?
没有
No.
但我不仅了下载情报
But I wasn't just downloading.
我还向服务器上传了数据
I was uploading onto the servers, too.
你上传了什么
What were you uploading?
特务  将他们的人录入系统
Clean skins. Their people into the system.
警卫
Guards!
警卫  警卫
Guards! Guards!
快走
Go.
我给他们加了电子标签
I tagged them.
我做的所有修改都加了电子标签
Everything I did, I tagged.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我做的所有修改都加了电子标签
Everything I did, I tagged.
是的  菲利普
Yes, Philip,
我迫于压力才供出了斯科特和斯顿布奇
giving up Scott and Stonebridge was a pressure decision.
但在当时
But in that moment,
我以为冒这个险是值得的
I thought it was a risk worth taking.
我相信他们有能力自保
I believe they can look after themselves.
你每次派他们执行任务  也都持有这个信念
You do the same every time you send them out there.
你敢说你不会做出同样的事吗
You tell me you wouldn't have done what I did.
至少我们现在知道了
Now at least we know the nature
朱海瑞所计划的袭击性质
of the attack al-Zuhari is planning.
是生化武器
We know it's bio-chemical...
我该怎么相信你说的是实话?
How do I even know that's true?
在贝鲁特发生了什么  李奥
What happened in Beirut, Leo?
在伊维尔路上
Yeah, what happened in Rue Eville,
道尔顿进入那房子之后发生了什么
when Dalton went into that house?
我中枪了
I was shot.
只是肩部中枪
In the shoulder.
你觉得一切都是我设计好的?
You think I engineered that?
我差点命丧黄泉
I could have died.
我图什么?  难道就换来这个结果?
And for what? For this?
你又在像在对待叛徒那样对待我
You are treating me like a fucking traitor again.
但你没死  不是吗
But you didn't die, though, did you?
而我的手下死了
One of my people did,
就跟凡·伯格...
just like Van Berg...
你觉得我当时能阻止她吗
Do you think I could have stopped her?
连你都控制不了她
You couldn't control her.
看在上帝的份上
For God's sake--
你到底信哪个上帝  李奥
And which God would that be, Leo?
这很重要吗
Does that matter?
我无法逼你信任我
I can't make you trust me.
你在这坐着
You stay there.
少校
Major.
上校
Colonel.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You OK? - Yeah.
关于他们带囚犯去的地方  有什么线索吗
You got anything on where they're taking the prisoners?
黑熊监狱北面百英里之内有9处可疑点
9 possibles within a hundred miles north of Black Bear.
我们在用无人侦察机追踪来往监狱的车辆
We've been using drones to track traffic from the prison,
但目前仍无线索
but so far we've got nothing.
迈克尔还能撑多久
How long has Michael got?
-任务的目标是阻止朱海瑞  -多久?
- This is about stopping al-Zuhari... - How long?
没多久了
Not long.
-李奥  -别问他
- Leo. - Don't ask.
到底发生了什么
What the fuck is going on?
俄罗斯特种部队已经待命
Spetsnaz team is on standby.
没有官方核准
Unofficial.
指挥官是我父亲的好友
The commander was a friend of my father.
谢谢你
Thank you.
是迈克尔
Michael.
中士
Sergeant?
长官
Boss.
报告情况
What's your sit-rep?
我还活着  达米恩和你们在一起吗
I'm alive. Is Damien with you?
我在这哥们  一切都好
Yeah, I'm here, bud. All good.
你在哪儿  迈克尔
Your location, Michael?
德列兹纳
Drezna.
他们为朱海瑞研发天花病毒的生化武器
They're developing weaponized smallpox for al-Zuhari.
黑熊监狱的囚犯们
The Black Bear prisoners
是测试对象
are the test subjects.
通知北约
Inform NATO.
我锁定了手机信号
I have a lock on the signal,
和德列兹纳地界匹配
and it's a match for Drezna.
长官  安德森已经被感染了
Boss, Andersson's been infected.
但他不仅仅
But he's not just
破解了数据
decoding data.
他还上传了数据
He was uploading.
上传了什么数据
Uploading what?
特务
Clean skins.
他把他们的特务录入了系统
He's been putting their people into the system.
特务的假身份
Fake IDs,
但他加上了某种电子标签
but he tagged them somehow.
迈克尔  我们拿到了解药  马上出发
Michael, we have your meds and we're on our way.
收到
Roger that.
迈克尔
Michael?
-李奥 听着  -什么都别说了
- Leo, look... - Nothing to say.
我们所有人都承受着巨大的压力
We're, all of us, under massive pressure.
听着  如果这天花病毒
Look, if this smallpox virus
确实在德列兹纳的实验室里
is at the Drezna facility,
那么直接进攻将会非常危险
then a frontal assault could be dangerous,
如果他们决定使用该武器  这甚至等同于自杀
suicidal, even, if they decide to use it.
还有  他们会趁你们尚未接近时
Also, chances are they will kill Stonebridge
杀掉斯顿布奇
before you get anywhere near him.
那怎么办  你打头阵?
So, what, you go in?
我会安全拿到病毒样本
I secure the virus safely,
至少也给斯顿布奇一个活下来的机会
at least give Stonebridge a chance.
朱海瑞的人之前就打算干掉你  李奥
Al-Zuhari's people tried to kill you before, Leo.
你进去有可能就出不来了
You walk in there, you're probably not gonna walk out.
菲利普  让我去吧
Philip, let me go in.
你就在外面  紧跟着我
You're outside. You come in after me.
不会有什么损失
You have nothing to lose.
瑞姆跟你一起
Richmond goes with you.
换便服
Civvies.
对  那就这么定了
Right. Let's get on with it.
我不确定  但我有非常糟糕的预感
I cannot be certain, but I have a bad, bad feeling
乌尔诺夫会在非常短的时间内
that Ulyanov wants to hand this virus off
把病毒交给朱海瑞的人
to al-Zuhari's people soon, very soon.
直升机已就位  德列兹纳离这三十公里
Helo's on stand-by. Drezna is 30 klicks from here.
我去联络特种部队  集合地点见
I'll go get Spetsnaz and we'll meet you there.
好了  我们五分钟后出发
Right. We're out of here in 5.
没问题吧
Are you up to this?
我得打个电话
I have to make a call.
给艾斯特吗
Ester?
发生了什么  你说你马上就回来的
What's going on? You said you'd be back by now.
没错  我还要在这待几天
Yeah...I'm gonna be a few more days here.
-不  你说过要回来的  -对
- Oh, no, but you said that you'd be back. - Yep.
我知道我说过的  但事情有变
I know what I said, but things change.
发生什么事了吗
Has something happened?
一切都很顺利  艾斯特
Ev-everything is fine, Ester.
等我回去之后  咱们就一起去玩
Listen, when I get back, we'll do something.
一起出去逛逛
We'll go out somewhere.
但我其实什么都不想做
But I don't really want to do anything,
只要  和你在一起
just...be together.
我觉得这样也不错
That sounds good to me.
你会照看好他的  对吧
And you'll look after him, won't you?
没错
Yeah.
我就是做这个的  孩子
It's what I do, kid.
谢谢你  达米恩
Thanks, Damien.
我爱你  爸爸
Love you, Dad.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你没事吧
You all right?
你该知道  我告诉过乌尔诺夫
You should know, I told Ulyanov
你和斯顿布奇在黑熊监狱里
you and Stonebridge were at Black Bear.
我知道
I know.
洛克已经告诉你了
Locke told you already.
达米恩  我当时进退两难
Damien, I was in a corner.
李奥
Leo...
我们都是棋子  仅此而已
we're all just pieces on a board, that's all.
一起去抓住那只大鸟吧
Let's go catch that bird.
我是菲利普·洛克
Philip Locke.
我是沃斯科夫上校
Colonel Voskov.
少校给你做过简报了吧
The Major briefed you?
-是的  -很好
- Yeah. - Good.
你那朋友
Your friend,
他会没事的
he'll be fine.
希望如此
Hope so.
你终于说了句人话
That was almost human.
好了  听着
All right, listen up.
你们去找斯顿布奇和病毒样本
You find Stonebridge and the viral samples,
剩下的事交给我们
we do the rest.
是
Sir.
找到斯顿布奇之后  立即给他用这个
When you get to Stonebridge, give him this right away.
行动吧
Let's move.
你没事吧
You all right?
是的
Yep.
他们在烧什么
What are they burning?
想着都不寒而栗
I dread to think.
李奥·卡马里
Leo Kamali.
他们进去了
They're in.
到了吗
Ok?
你来这儿做什么  卡马里
What are you doing here, Kamali?
执行朱海瑞的命令
Following al-Zuhari's orders.
李扎·哈桑应该来取包裹了
Reza Hassan is supposed to be collecting the packet.
以现下的形势
Ah, in times like these,
还是谨慎点好
a little insurance is wise.
乌尔诺夫在哪儿
Where's Ulyanov?
和哈桑在来的路上
On his way with Hassan.
这位是谁
Who is this?
她是我的人
She's with me.
你让那个美国人跑了
You let the American escape.
我们抓住了英国人
We have the Englishman.
很好
Good.
我们进去吧
Let's go in.
他在里面
He is in here.
我会用这个人做实体演示
I will demonstrate on this man.
乌尔诺夫先生希望亲手了结他
Mr. Ulyanov wishes to take care of him in person.
他们来了
They are here.
李扎·哈桑
Reza Hassan.
如果朱海瑞要对付卡马里  那他可有麻烦了
If al-Zuhari's on to Kamali, he's in trouble.
乌尔诺夫
Ulyanov.
我帮你干掉他
I'll flip you for him.
他是我的
He's mine.
行动
Move.
B2就位
Bravo Two in position.
待命
Stand by.
愿真主与你同在
Assalamu alaikum.
大限就要到了  兄弟
她是我们的人
也许你离开我们太久了
我奉命来和你联络
是他吗
动手吧
Do it.
就是现在
It's now or never.
行动
Go.
操你妈的
Motherfucker!
你个贱人
Oh, you bitch!
你没事吧
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
迈克尔在哪儿
Where's Michael?
那边过去
Through there.
欠我一瓶啤酒
You owe me a beer.
欠你妹
You wish.
你要找到钥匙
Hey, you need a key!
什么
Huh?
钥匙
Key!
找到了
Got one.
迈克
Hey, Mikey.
你还好吗
You all right?
你能出现真是太好了
It's nice of you to show up.
再来早点你就不感激我了是吧
Yeah, well, any sooner and you wouldn't have appreciated it, huh?
他们在你身上做了什么奇怪的实验吗
They do any funny experiments on you?
去你妈
Oh, fuck.
往你屁股上戳针了吗
Pricks in your ass?
此处双关  亦指"操你菊花了吗"
赶紧带我出去
Just get me the hell out of here.
来吧  给
All right. Here you go.
干的好
Nice work.
把这个注射进去
Get that in you.
六点方向  六点方向
On your 6! On your 6!
给  迈克
Here. Mikey.
一比零
One up.
谢了
Thank you.
好了
Ok.
你能走吗
Think you can walk?
能
Yeah.
我能跟上你
I can keep up with you.
是吗
Yeah?
我已经感觉好多了
Feel better already.
真的吗
Really?
才怪
No.
该死的
Oh, shit.
上
Go!
迈克
Mikey!
该死
Shit.
可怜的家伙
Poor bastard.
迈克  有人来了
Mike, comin' at us.
这边  迈克
This way, Mike.
这边
This way.
乌尔诺夫
Ulyanov!
妮娜·皮拉戈娃在此
Nina Pirogova.
乌尔诺夫
Ulyanov!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
操
Fuck!
该死
Oh, shit!
卡马里
Kamali!
把病毒给我
Give me the virus!
别动
Stay there!
掩护我
Cover me!
快  快过来
Come! Come!
快出去  快走
Out! Quick! Move!
总部  封锁大楼
Zero, seal the building.
他们拿到了病毒
They have the virus.
自己人
He's with us.
自己人  跟我一起的
He's all right. He's with me.
你没事吧
You all right?
乌尔诺夫呢
Ulyanov?
你说的对
You were right.
总是在紧要关头掉链子
Always run out at the worst time.
他们抓到了卡马里
They got Kamali.
兄弟  你这次得自己上了
Buddy, I got to sit this one out.
明白
Got it.
我没事
It's all right.
谢谢
Cheers.
结果怎么样
So...what's the prognosis?
这次行动算不上失败
Well, I won't call it a mission failure.
他们得到了武器  但我们拿到了样本
They have a weapon, but we have samples,
还有瓦丽妮  那个瑞典医生
and Valigny, the Swedish doctor.
我也许能从她嘴里问出点东西
I might get something out of her.
瑞姆和北约的计算机小组一起
Richmond, she's with the NATO forensic computer team,
试图找出安德森上传的特务身份
see if they can find the clean skins uploaded by Andersson.
其实我问的是我的诊断结果
Actually, I was asking about my prognosis.
是嘛  你好得很
Oh. Ah, you'll be fine.
没什么好担心的
It's nothing to worry about.
你感染了一种叫作肉毒杆菌的细菌
It was a bacterium called clostridium botulinum.
不过你的确差点就没救了
It was a close one.
李奥怎么样了
What about Leo?
没有消息
There's no news.
如果不是他  你早就死了
If it wasn't for him, you would be dead.
他赌上了自己的性命
He risked his life.
他竭尽全力阻止他们得到病毒
He did everything he could to stop them getting the virus,
而我之前却不信任他
and I didn't trust him.
我以为...
I thought it was--
这不能怪你
This is not on you.
曾经
You know, there was a...
有一瞬间
a moment...
我感觉自己快死了
where I could feel myself going...
只想痛快的作个了断
and I wanted it to end.
死了也比残废强
Best dead than broken, you know?
现在呢
And now?
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
想听实话吗  迈克尔
You want to know the truth, Michael?
我们活不到毛主席的年纪
We don't make good old men.
多吃点葡萄
Enjoy the grapes.
是
Boss.
哪位
Who is it?
联邦安全局
FSB.
你个死人快开门
Open the fucking door.
请进
Come in.
你要对我用哪个
Which one are you intending to use?
还不知道
Don't know yet.
你喜欢哪个
What kind of mood are you in?
你想看看俄罗斯姑娘是怎么喝伏特加的吗
Do you want me to show you how a Russian girl drinks her vodka?
必须的
Yes, I do.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
什么
What?
说英语
Say it in English.
干我
Fuck me.
你刚才说的是这个?  真的假的
Is that what you were saying? Really?
对
Yeah.
你说了很多遍
You say that a lot.
不是吧
Oh, my God.
去他妈的电话
Fuck that.
是谁
What's that?
管他呢
It's nothing.
怎么了
What's up?
我叫李奥·卡马里
My name is Leo Kamali.
我忏悔  我冒犯了真主安拉
"I confess I have sinned against Allah
玷污了他最钟爱的名字
and defiled his most blessed name."
我以异教徒"大魔鬼"的名义
"I have betrayed him in the name of the infidel,
伊朗在其外交辞令中用"大魔鬼"特指美英政府
背叛了真主
"The Great Satan.
我在此传递消息一则
"And I am here to deliver this message."
朱海瑞会以史无前例的方式
"Al-Zuhari will bring down a vengeance upon the West,
向西方世界复仇
"The like of which has never been seen.
受其恩典  我将死的干净利落
"My fate is a pure and merciful one
可今后更多的殉难者将生不如死
compared with the victims to come."
他妈的
Fuck!
我该怎么对那个小女孩交待
What am I gonna say to that little girl?
李奥说朱海瑞为达目标
Leo told us al-Zuhari would sacrifice anything,
可以牺牲一切  不择手段
pay any price to achieve his goals,
为了打倒他  我们必须以牙还牙
and in order to defeat him, we would have to do the same.
我丑话说在前头  牺牲再多
Well, I'm telling you now that whatever the sacrifice...
也要拼到最后
it will be made.
代价再大
And whatever the price,
亦不足惜
it will be paid.